<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Learning from Error</title>
    <link>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Learning from Error</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:07:24 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="adarshmathew.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Demographic Bias in Model Design and Big Tech</title>
      <link>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/demo-bias-big-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:07:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/demo-bias-big-tech/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s weekly CSS Workshop, we had a duo from AirBnB presenting work on &amp;lsquo;Designing for Trust&amp;rsquo; in the context of the sharing economy. The paper had an interesting design &amp;ndash; they set up an investment game to construct their dependent variable of &amp;lsquo;Trust&amp;rsquo;, and used the participants&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;behavioural&amp;rsquo; data logs to identify what behaviours predicted propensity to trust among users. They had a particularly interesting &amp;lsquo;data triangulation&amp;rsquo; step, where they measured the validity of their trust construct using good ol&amp;rsquo; survey data, all to see if their construct was capturing the right indicators of trust in a completely different context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 01:05:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Testing what this looks like.
Ideally, I&amp;rsquo;d be able to do a whole new layout for the about page. Let&amp;rsquo;s see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/kp_syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/kp_syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Syllabus &amp;ndash; Knowledge &amp;amp; Politics Hi everyone,
Please see the draft syllabus for Knowledge and Politics, below. This course is primarily aimed at graduate students but is open to a limited number of advanced undergraduates as well. If you are an undergraduate interested in enrolling in the course, please send me an email.
PLSC 42502: Knowledge and Politics: Winter 2020 Tuesdays 9:30-12:20, Foster 105
Instructor: Matthew Landauer (landauer@uchicago.edu)
DRAFT SYLLABUS: READINGS AND ASSIGNMENTS SUBJECT TO CHANGE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/w1_kp_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adarshmathew.github.io/posts/w1_kp_notes/</guid>
      <description>Goldman paper Individual Epistemology: (traditional) Mental ps of cognitive agents in isolation or abstraction from other persons.
Social Epistemology: Social paths to knowledge; many routes to belief that feature interactions with other agents
Veritistic Epistemology: Prod of knowledge (true belief), error (false belief), ignorance (absence of true belief)
 Main question for veritistic epistemology is: Which practices have a comparatively favorable impact on knowledge as contrasted with error and ignorance?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>